export default [
  {
    question: "Who was the best football player of Europe in 1998?",
    choice1: "Marcel Desailly from Milan and Chelsea",
    choice2: "Lilian Thuram from Parma",
    choice3: "Zinedine Zidane from Juventus",
    choice4: "Michael Owen from Liverpool",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "When was the first Premier League played?",
    choice1: "1891-92",
    choice2: "1952-53",
    choice3: "1985-86",
    choice4: "1992-93",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In 1990, this team failed to score even one goal in the World Cup final",
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Brazil",
    choice3: "Paris Saint-Germain",
    choice4: "Portugal",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Whcih played scores the fastest hat-trick in Premier League",
    choice1: "Eric Cantona",
    choice2: "Sadio Mane",
    choice3: "Brian Deane",
    choice4: "Rod Wallace",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Barcalona player was jailed after it was found that his password was fake?",
    choice1: "Jordi Alba",
    choice2: "Martin Braithwaite",
    choice3: "Ronald Araujo",
    choice4: "Ronaldinho",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first Premier League manager who was fired?",
    choice1: "Ian Porterfield",
    choice2: "George Graham",
    choice3: "Stewart Houston",
    choice4: "Bruce Rioch",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "When was the original FA Cup Trophy Stolen? ",
    choice1: "1900",
    choice2: "1885",
    choice3: "1895",
    choice4: "1845",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how many games did Cristiano Ronaldo score his first Champions League goal?",
    choice1: "27",
    choice2: "17",
    choice3: "5",
    choice4: "36",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which club did Nicky Byrne play before finding his calling in Music?",
    choice1: "Everton",
    choice2: "Leeds United",
    choice3: "Tottenham",
    choice4: "Manchester City",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Liverpool was founded in which year?",
    choice1: "1890",
    choice2: "1950",
    choice3: "1892",
    choice4: "1991",
    answer: 3,
  },
];
